We sigh whenever we're about to come to a standstill
終わりなき旅の途中　立ち止まりそうな時
Owarinaki tabi no tochuu tachidomarisouna toki
While moving on this endless journey.
深いため息こぼす　僕らは
Fukai tameiki kobosu bokura wa
Everytime we lunge for it, it escapes and flies off.
掴みかけてはまた離れていった
Tsukamikaketewa mata hanareteitta
But now, there's nothing to be afraid of
でも今はもう何も恐れることはない
Demo ima wa mou nanimo osoreru koto wa nai
The powerful ties that bind our hearts
心を繋ぐ強い絆は
Kokoro wo tsunagu tsuyoi kizuna wa
Will never come loose.
けして解けはしないさ
Keshite hodoke wa shinai sa
After a lifetime of searching, we finally arrived
探し続けて辿り着いた
Sagashitsuzukete tadoritsuita
Here, where the period lies.
この場所で Period に
Kono basho de piriodo ni
Let's change all our sorrow and rage to power.
悲しみ怒り 力に変えて
Kanashimi ikari chikara ni kaete
Destiny is right within our reach.
運命はすぐそばに
Unmei wa sugu soba ni
Do you remember the first time we met, Kimblee?
覚えているか　キンブリー
初めて会った時のことを
It seems our positions are now reversed!
あの時とは逆だな
Don't you dare look down on me!
私を見下ろすな
Kimblee, you bastard!
キンブリー　てめぇ
なんで　なんでウィンリィがここにいる
Why... Why is Winry here?!
せっかくスカーを追い詰めたのに
We were just about to capture Scar, but now he's taken her hostage!
人質に取られちまったじゃねぇか
Move.
どきなさい
Idiot!
バカ野郎
Stop, Crimson Alchemist!
やめろ　紅蓮の錬金術師
Do you not see Winry in front of you?!
ウィンリィの姿が目に入らねぇのか
Don't get in my way!
邪魔をしないでいただきたい
Hold it, Scar!
待ちなさい　スカー
Sir Kimblee, don't go near the building! It's dangerous!
キンブリーさん
建物に近づいては危険です
撤収
Withdraw!
There's a blizzard approaching! Hurry!
吹雪が来るぞ
急げ
You're a fantastic actor.
迫真の演技だったな
That wasn't an act.
演技なんかじゃねぇよ
I'm actually furious at myself for being such a coward and having to put up such an act.
こんな三文芝居を打たなきゃならなかった
自分のふがいなさに
マジではらわたが煮えくり返る
Why did you kill my parents?
なんで　父さんと母さんを殺したの
No matter what I say, it'll be only an excuse.
何を言っても言い訳にしかならん
The fact is I killed the Rockbells.
オレがロックベルという医者夫婦を殺したのは事実だ
With this hand...
この手で
Girl, you have the right to kill me.
娘よ　お前にはオレを裁く資格がある
At this rate, you'll die from blood loss.
腕　このままだと失血死しちゃう
Winry!
ウィンリィ
分かってる
I know.
But I'm sure Mom and Dad would have done the same.
でも　父さんと母さんも多分こうしただろうから
父さんと母さんが生かした命だもの
It's a life Mom and Dad saved.
I'm sure there's a meaning to it.
何か意味があるんだと思う
You're saying you'll forgive me?
オレを許すというのか
Don't get the wrong idea! I haven't forgiven you for killing my parents unjustly!
勘違いしないで
理不尽を許してはいないのよ
Winry...
ウィンリィ
大丈夫　泣かないよ
Don't worry; I'm not going to cry.
次に泣く時はうれし泣きだって　約束したから
Didn't I promise you that the next time I cry, it'd be with tears of joy?
Hey, Scar.
おい　スカー
Despite what Winry just said, I still want to beat you to a pulp and drag you over to the Rockbells' graves.
ウィンリィはこう言うけどな
オレはてめぇを殴り倒して
ロックベル家の墓の前に
引きずり出してやりてぇぐらいだ
Should I contact Headquarters?
本部に連絡しますか
Yeah.
ああ
I believe Miles was your name?
マイルズといったか
Can I ask something?
一つ聞いていいか
What is it?
なんだ
You called me a fellow countryman, didn't you?
オレのことを同族と言ったな
I did.
そうだ　祖父の代までイシュヴァール人だった
Until my grandfather's generation, my ancestors were full Ishbalans.
I wish we could have met under different circumstances, my red-eyed brethren.
こんな会い方はしたくなかったな
赤い目の同胞よ
Why are you siding with the Amestrian army?
なぜアメストリス国軍に加担する
この国の内側から
Because I wish to change the way people feel about Ishbalans from within the country.
イシュヴァール人に対する人々の意識を変えるためだ
I doubt people would change the way they feel so easily.
そうやすやすと人の心が変わるとは思えん
いつまで掛かるか分からん
I don't know how long it'll take.
But there are things only I,
a man of mixed parentage, can do.
だが　混血の私だからこそできることがある
I'm nothing but an Ishbalan pebble that was thrown into the Amestrian army.
この身はアメストリス国軍に投じられた
イシュヴァールの一石
But there may come a time when
a small ripple becomes a giant wave.
小さな波紋が
やがて大きな波となるときが来るかもしれん
And ironically, the person who made me realize that is a full-blooded Amestrian.
そしてそのことに気づかせてくれたのは
皮肉なことに生っ粋のアメストリス人だった
I'm nothing but a mass of hatred, born from that civil war.
オレはあの内乱で生まれた憎しみという名の膿だ
I'm glad someone like you exists.
貴様のようなヤツがいてくれてよかった
Major.
少佐
Is this Headquarters?
本部か　こちらマイルズ
This is Miles speaking.
We've captured Scar in a building in Area D.
エリアＤのビルでスカーを捕らえた
Let Kimblee know.
キンブリーに伝えてくれ
No matter what your circumstances are,
I can't just let you go.
貴様にどんな事情があるにせよ
見逃すわけにはいかない
You deserve to be tried and sentenced.
しかるべき裁きを受けろ
Wait!
待ってくれ
Who are you?!
誰だ
May!
メイ
Doctor Marcoh!
マルコーさん
Please don't take that man away.
その男を連れていかないでくれ
This is bad, Sir Kimblee.
これはまずいですね　キンブリーさん
The clouds are moving fast.
The weather's about to get pretty ugly.
雲が速い
こりゃ荒れてきますよ
Then let's hurry.
急ぎなさい
Deciphering research documents?
研究書の解読
It's breakthrough research that combines the alchemies from Amestris and Xing!
アメストリスの錬金術とシンの錬丹術との融合を試みた
画期的な研究なんです
But the essential portions are written in ancient Ishbalan.
しかし 肝心な所が
古代イシュヴァール語で書かれている
The only one who can read this is Scar.
これが読めるのはスカーしかいない
So...
だから
You're the girl who knows Eastern Alchemy, right?
錬丹術の娘だな
I've received orders to take you back to the fort.
お前を砦に連れてくるよう命令を受けている
Huh?! M-Me?
えっ　わ　私ですか
Don't worry.
安心しろ　手厚く迎えろとのことだ
I've been ordered to give you a warm reception.
Now... if Scar can't be caught...
さて　スカーが捕まるわけにもいかず
マルコーがここにいることも知られてはまずいとなると
...and if we also can't let them know that Marcoh is here...
It might be better to just hide them at Briggs for now.
いっそみんなまとめて
ブリッグズ砦に匿うのがいいかもしれんな
Hang on, what the hell?!
ちょっと待てよ　なんだよそれ
You're taking him, too?!
こいつも連れてくってのかよ
Don't you guys need him to decipher the documents?
研究書の解読に必要なんだろ
こんなヤツの力を借りるなんて
It pisses me off to think we have to ask him  for help...
Why don't we just hand him over to Kimblee and-
とっととキンブリーに引き渡して
A transmutation circle made from this country.
国土錬成陣
And the history of this country.
そしてこの国の成り立ち
I've heard everything from General Armstrong.
アームストロング少将から聞いているぞ
Something is about to happen;
something that will encompass all of Amestris.
アメストリス全土を巻き込んで
何かが起ころうとしている
Isn't deciphering the documents of higher priority than anything else?
研究書の解読は
何にも増して重要なのではないか
I'm also aware that Ms. Rockbell has been taken hostage.
ロックベルのお嬢さんが
人質にされていることは聞いている
If we do this now, we could make Kimblee take the blame and hide her away at the same time.
今ならキンブリーに泥をかぶせて
彼女を匿うこともできる
Scar, if you decide to lend us a hand,
we can postpone your trial to a later date.
スカーよ
我々に協力するなら裁きは後に延ばそう
What do you say?
どうだ
I have no other options, do I?
ほかに選択の余地はないのだろう
I promise to cooperate.
協力を約束する
Do you really mean it?
偽りないか
イシュヴァールの血に懸けて
I swear on my Ishbalan blood, my red-eyed brethren.
赤い目の同胞よ
So, that's how it is.
そういうわけだ
I'm sorry, but you're going to have to wait a little longer for him to face trial.
すまない　お嬢さん
この者の裁きはしばらく待ってくれ
That's fine.
はい
Oh yeah, I forgot about these two.
そういえばこいつらのことを忘れていたな
Kill them.
始末しろ
Roger.
はっ
H-Hey!
おい
Hang on! You don't have to kill them!
ちょっと待ってよ　何も殺すこと
There's nothing to be gained from letting them live.
生かしておいて得がない　やれ
Do it.
This isn't about gain or loss! Isn't there something you could do besides killing them?!
いや　得とかじゃなくて
殺さずに済む方法はないの
Showing us pity, huh?
ふん　オレたちに情けをかけるってか
There's no need for that. You're just a kid who doesn't know anything.
余計なお世話だ　何も知らん甘ちゃんが
There's no future for us anyway, since we've got bodies like these.
どうせこんな体じゃあ　先は見えてる
If you're going to kill us, just do it.
殺すんなら殺せ
Don't you two have family or people important to you?
おじさんたち　家族とか大切な人はいないの
Of course we do.
いるさ
But when we were transformed to this state, we were publicly pronounced dead.
だがこの体になった時我々は死んだことにされた
I haven't seen them since.
以来　会ってない
Don't you want  to see them?
会いたいとは思わない
Even if we did, there's nothing we could do. Look at us.
会いたくてもしょうがないだろ　このナリじゃ
Oh, so you don't want to return to your old selves?
へえ　じゃあもう元の体に戻りたいと思わないんだ
You're fine with those bodies, then?
その体で満足しちゃってるんだね
んなわけあるか
Of course not!
戻りたいに決まってんだろうが
Of course we want to return to normal!
Then there's your answer.
それが答えだろ
Please don't talk as though you've already given up.
どうせとか　しょうがないとか
枯れたこと言わないでよ
You haven't even explored the possibility of returning to your old bodies.
元の体に戻れる可能性を探りもしないでさ
ふん　貴様にオレたちの何が分かる
How the hell would you  know how we feel?!
There's no way to-
戻れる可能性なんか
I'm going to get my body back.
僕は戻るよ
No matter how many years it may take, I'll never give up!
この先何年掛かろうと
諦めたりはしない
Major!
少佐
What is it?
どうした
まずいです
This isn't good.
A blizzard is approaching.
吹雪になります
It's impossible to march in a blizzard with the equipment we have right now.
ここにある装備では雪中行軍は無理だ
At this rate, we won't make it back to the fort.
このままでは砦に辿り着けなくなる
What should we do?
どうしよう
Isn't this a mining town?
ここ鉱山の町だろ
Why don't we just take the underground mining path?
地下坑道を行けばいいんじゃないのか
Wh-What?!
なっ　なんだよ
I-It's just that since this is such a big mine, I figured there might be a path leading through the mountain...
いっ　いや　こんだけでかい鉱山なら
山一つ越えた所まで坑道がつながっていると
I-I think...
お　思う
That's it!
それだ
Sir Yoki!
ヨキさん
I used to own a coal mine, after all!
元炭鉱経営者をなめるなよ
That would work! The mine exits beyond the mountain.
行けます
山の向こうに坑道が出てます
Okay.
よし
If you happen to encounter a soldier from Briggs, hand them this.
砦のブリッグズ兵に会ったら
これを渡すといい
I've stated the situation in there, so they should give you refuge.
中に事情が書いてあるから
匿ってくれるだろう
I'm in your debt.
すまない
I guess the only thing we still have to account for is the girl.
あと問題はお嬢さんだな
我々と行動を共にするのはいいとして
Even if she comes with us, wouldn't the Elric Brothers be the prime suspects if they find out she's missing?
行方が知れなくなったとなると
真っ先にエルリック兄弟が疑われるんじゃないか
We'll figure something out.
なんとかなりますよ
Don't mean to brag, but we can work as well as we can talk.
自慢じゃないが　口八丁手八丁なら
No, Kimblee is a very suspicious man.
いや　猜疑心の強いキンブリーのことだ
If we don't plan this completely, he'll be doubly suspicious.
半端なことをすれば余計に怪しまれる
Umm... this may be a bit strange coming from me...
あの　自分でこんなこと言うのもなんだけど
But...
その
What if I were kidnapped by Scar?
私がスカーに連れ去られるっていうのはどうかな
連れ去られるって
"Kidnapped"?
それはつまり　あれか
So... what you mean is...
We free him, and...
こいつを解放して
Yeah. Scar runs off with me in his arms, and you pretend like you're desperately trying to stop him...
そう　スカーが私を抱えて逃げる
それをエドたちが必死で止めようとするってところを
追っ手に見せる　みたいな
...or something like that.
Do you think we'll let you do something that dangerous?!
んな危ないことできるか
I'm a hostage right now, anyway!
命握られてるのよ
I have to risk my life to escape, or it'll never happen!
それなら　こっちも命懸けで逃げなきゃ逃げきれないよ
But with Scar?!
でも　スカーと一緒なんて
そうだ　お前が命懸ける必要はない
Yeah! You don't need to risk your  life!
そうやっていつもいつも
Quit trying to do everything by yourselves! I'm tired of it!
あんたたちだけで全部抱え込まないでよ
Hurry up and decide. The blizzard is coming.
早く決めろ
吹雪が迫ってきている
じきにここから一歩も出られなくなるぞ
Pretty soon, we won't even be able to leave this building.
Kimblee's squad is here!
キンブリー隊が見えました
ちくしょ
Dammit!
スカー　余計なことしやがったら
Scar, if anything happens...
分かっている　約束は守ろう
I know. I plan to keep my promise.
オレたちも
Could you...
オレたちも連れていってくれ
Could you take us, as well?
信用されてないのは分かる
I understand you don't trust us,
so you can keep us bound.
だから　手かせはしたままで構わない
キンブリー様は仕事のできない部下に容赦がない
Sir Kimblee shows no mercy to men who can't do their job.
We'll get killed either way.
どのみち殺される
And besides...
それに
オレたちも諦めたくない
...we don't want to give up, either!
信じていいんだね
We can trust you, right?
If you two happen to betray us and get in our way, this country could fall to ruin.
君たちがもし私たちの邪魔をしたら
この国は滅ぶかもしれんのだよ
君たちの大切な人も含めてね
Including the people you two hold dear.
Hang on! What do you mean?!
ちょっと待て　なんだそれは
Central never told us anything like that!
中央軍ではそんな話　聞かされてない
詳しく教えてくれ
Tell us the details! What is this about?!
どういうことだ
これでいいのか
Is this fine?
ああ　その方がそちらさんも安心だろ
Yeah. You all will probably feel safer this way, too.
スカー　ひと芝居頼むぞ
Scar, we're going to have to ask you to put on an act.
分かっている
I know.
Keep the vow you swore on your Ishbalan blood.
誓いは守れよ
イシュヴァールの血に懸けて
Hey! You need to take off your earrings!
お嬢ちゃん　耳　ピアス
Those are made out of metal, aren't they?
それ金属製だろ
外しとかないと凍傷になるよ
If you don't take them off, you'll get frostbite.
Ed.
エド
Hold on to these for me.
これ　預かっといて
砦で待ってるから
I'll be waiting for you at the fort!
キンブリー　てめぇ
Kimblee, you bastard!
なんで　ちゃんとウィンリィを見てなかった
Why the hell didn't you keep an eye on Winry?!
ザンパノとジェルソが心配だな
I'm worried about Zampano and Jerso.
スカーにやられたか
They were either killed by Scar, or they can't move because of the blizzard...
この吹雪で動けないでいるのか
Scar shouldn't be able to move, either.
動けないのはスカーも同じ
He has to be in this town somewhere!
必ずこの町のどこかにいます
We ought to plan our next search while we're sitting here!
今のうちに　再捜索の手はずを整えましょう
まったく　この吹雪には助けられたな
This blizzard really saved us...
今のうちに砦に辿り着いてくれよ
I pray that all of you will make it to the fort.
マイルズ少佐
Major Miles, you have a phone call from Briggs.
ブリッグズから通信です
マイルズだ
Miles speaking.
なんだと
What?!
Oh, so you're the daughter of those Rockbells.
じゃあ　君はあのロックベル夫妻の娘さんなのか
両親をご存じなんですか
You've heard of my parents?
There isn't a single doctor who was in Ishbal who hasn't.
イシュヴァールを経験した医者で
彼らの名前を知らぬ者はいないよ
我が身を顧みずに医者の本分を貫いたと
They fulfilled their duties as doctors without any regard for their own lives.
I haven't forgiven that you killed my parents unjustly!
理不尽を許してはいないのよ
You must endure.
耐えねばならんのだよ
So you're telling me to forgive the army for what they did?
国軍のしたことを許せというのですか
耐えると許すは違う
"Enduring" and "forgiving" are two different things.
世の理不尽を許してはいかん
You must not forgive the unjustness of society.
As a human being, you must hold the event in contempt.
人として憤らねばならん
Yet, you must endure.
だが　耐えねばならぬ
憎しみの連鎖は絶たねばならぬ
You must put an end to the chain of hatred!
If many negative emotions gather,
they will end up influencing the entire world.
負の感情が集まれば
世界は負の流れになってしまう
But on the other hand, it is also possible to gather positive emotions and lead the world in that direction.
逆に正の感情を集めて
世界を正の流れにすることもできる
そのために私は錬金術を学んでいるんだ
That is why I study alchemy.
おっ　ここだ　ここだ
Oh, here we are.
なんだ　ここは
What is this place?
坑内係員詰め所だよ
It's a post for mine officers.
ここなら
There should be...
おっ　あった
Ah, found it.
See? A detailed map of the mine.
ほら　坑道の詳細な地図だ
It looks pretty complicated.
複雑だな　何がなんだか分からん
I don't understand what goes where.
We can just take this path here, you see?
こう　こう　こう抜ければいいんだよ
Wow, you're pretty amazing.
ほう　あんたすごいな
へへへっ　もっと褒めろ
Keep the compliments coming!
この分なら
With this, we should be able to reach the other side of the mountain a lot faster than we thought we would.
思ったより早く山の向こうへ抜けられそうだな
なあ　マルコー先生よ
Hey, Doctor Marcoh... Do you think those research documents hold anything to get us back to our old bodies?
あの研究書に俺達が元の体に戻るヒントは
あるんだろうか
可能性はある
There is a possibility.
It's tough to say because it's not a form of alchemy we're familiar with.
何せ私たちの知らない錬金術だからな
I've got faith, Doctor!
期待してるぜ　先生
I really want to see my family!
ああ　早く家族に会いてぇなぁ
くふふっ　あれだけ女房の尻に敷かれてたくせに
Even though your wife was always leading you by the nose?
You probably only want to see your daughter.
会いたいのは娘にだけじゃないのか
Look who's talking! You always turn nasty when you're drunk, so your son was just about fed up with you.
そういうお前こそ
酒癖が悪くて
息子に愛想つかされてたじゃないか
You still have the guts to see him now?
今更会わせる顔あるのか
That was brutal.
言いやがる
Is something wrong, May?
どうかしたのかい　メイちゃん
いえ
No.
私も国の一族が待っているのに
I was just wondering when I'll be able to return, since my people are waiting for me...
いつ帰れるかと思うと
The philosopher's stone uses the lives of humans.
生きている人々を材料にする賢者の石
そんなものを求めるわけにはまいりません
I mustn't seek such a thing.
石はなくても
Even if I tell him how to create one,
without bringing back an actual stone,
作り方を知れば
the Emperor would make plans to create one without hesitation.
皇帝陛下は躊躇なくそれを試すでしょう
By sacrificing the lives of many people...
大勢の人々を犠牲にして
不老不死　一体どうすれば
Immortality... Just what should I do?
That answer may also be hidden in those research documents.
その答えも
もしかしたら研究書に載っているかもしれないよ
早く砦にたどりついてじっくり読み解こう
So let's try to get to the fort as quickly as we can to decipher them.
はい
You're right.
The fort is no longer safe?!
砦が安全じゃなくなった
Major General Armstrong has been summoned to Central.
アームストロング少将が
セントラルに呼び出しをくらった
砦にも中央軍が大勢入ってきている
Many soldiers from Central are now stationed at the fort, as well.
おそらくキンブリーの進言に違いない
Kimblee must have proposed it.
He was making quite a few phone calls while at the fort, after all.
砦にいた時
やけにこまめに電話を入れていたからな
待てよ　少将がいなくなったら
Hang on. If the Major General is no longer there...
An officer loyal to Bradley is going to be stationed there.
代わりにブラッドレイの息のかかった
指揮官が配置される
So, Winry and the rest of them...
じゃあ　ウィンリィたちは
It's going to be a lot more difficult to hide them there now.
匿うのが難しくなった
それどころか　下手をしたら敵の手中に
That's hardly the issue. If things take a turn for the worse, they could fall in the hands of the enemy...
なんとかウィンリィたちに知らせないと
We have to let them know somehow!
It would be impossible to go after them in this blizzard.
この吹雪の中　追いかけるのは不可能だ
But we can't just leave them!
だからってほうっておけるか
I'm going.
オレは行くぞ
An amateur shouldn't take a blizzard lightly!
素人が吹雪をなめるんじゃない
It'll suck out all your strength in a matter of minutes, leaving you to freeze to death.
あっという間に体力を奪われ　凍え死ぬぞ
There's another option.
あるよ　方法
There's someone here with a body that knows no fatigue and won't freeze.
疲れを知らない体を持っていて
凍え死にもしない人間
This is worse than I expected...
こりゃ想像以上だ
Now, where's the landmark...
えっと　目印目印っと
あった
There!
I can't see anything with the snow blowing everywhere.
真っ白で何も見えない
なんだ今の
What was that just now? My body?!
僕の肉体
Why?
なんで
It's impossible to place a soul on a body that doesn't belong.
そもそも別々の肉体と魂を
一緒にしようってのが無理なんだよ
本来　魂が入ってはならない体
A body that shouldn't possess a soul...
拒絶反応
A rejection reaction!
僕の肉体が魂を引っ張ってる
My old body is pulling my soul towards it!
Come on! Get it together!
しっかりしろ　しっかりするんだ
急がなきゃ
I have to hurry.
アルフォンス·エルリック
Alphonse Elric.
Edward Elric.
エドワード·エルリック
そして
And...
...Van Hohenheim.
ヴァン·ホーエンハイム
Izumi Curtis is also a possibility.
イズミ·カーティスも可能性あり
Just one more.
あと一人
The promise we never made
交わしたはずのない約束が
Kawashita hazu no nai yakasoku ga
yet again
今日も
Kyou mo
tries to snatch our future away from us.
僕らの未来を奪おうとする
Bokura no mirai wo ubaou to suru
Why is it that we can't rejoice
欲しがっていたものを手にしても
Hoshigatteita mono wo te ni shitemo
straight from the heart
素直に
Sunao ni
when we obtain something we've always been after?
うまく笑えないのはなぜだろう
Umaku waraenai nowa nazedarou
The overflowing tears aren't from feebleness or remorse.
あふれる涙は　弱さや後悔じゃない
Afureru namida wo yowasa ya koukai ja nai
They're fragments born from agony.
イタミが生んだカケラで
Itami ga unda kakera de
Of all the moments and destinies,
どんな瞬間だって運命だって
Donna shunkan datte unmei datte
I realized there's one absolute certainty.
ひとつだけ確かなものがあると知った
Hitotsu dake tashika na mono ga aru to shitta
Even if things get tough and I'm at my limit
限界だって困難だって
Genkai datte konnan datte
I refuse to give up.
あきらめたくないよ
Akirametakunaiyo
Please, don't let go.
このまま離さないで
Konomama hanasanaide
I can feel the warmth of your right hand
かたく握りしめた　君の右手のぬくもり
Kataku nigirishimeta kimi no migite no nukumori
where it's tightly joined with my left.
ここにあるから
Koko ni arukara
未知の世界への旅立ち
A departure toward an unknown world.
日本語字幕仕上げ：FAYFAY
It's due to one's heart seeking something new.
それは新しいものを求める心
漫遊字幕組
http://popgo.net/bbs
人ならば心を止めることはできない
A human can never go against the wishes of his heart,
but conflict always arises in that moment.
だが　そこには必ず軋轢が生じる
次回　鋼の錬金術師
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
FULLMETAL ALCHEMIST
Episode 40, Homunculus.
第四十話　フラスコの中の小人
The righteous isn't the one to win.
正しい者が勝つのではない
The one to overcome the boundaries shall stand as the winner.
壁を乗り越えた者が勝つのだ